const questions = [
     {
	id:1,
	question: "This farm 'yielded' very well this year.",
	answer_a:"produce",
	answer_b:"performance",
	answer_c:"scarce",
	answer_d:"fall down",
	correct_answer: "a"
     },
     {
    	id: 2,
    	question: "Jannet did't appreciate her boss''dig' about her hairstyle.",
        answer_a: "critic",
        answer_b: "compliment",
        answer_c: "hole",
        answer_d: "critical remark",
        correct_answer: "d"
     },
     {
	id: 3,
        question: "The assistant 'ushered' the visitor to the boss's office",
        answer_a: "asked",
        answer_b: "showed",
        answer_c: "walked someone to position",
        answer_d: "assigned",
        correct_answer: "c"
      },
      {
	id: 4,
        question: "American officials are fearful of upending trade negotiations since they could be harmful ",
        answer_a: "v. improve",
        answer_b: "v. deny",
        answer_c: "v. cut",
        answer_d: "v. change drastically",
        correct_answer: "d"
      },
      {
	id: 5,
        question: " Elizabeth always dithers for a while before she acts",
        answer_a: "v. think",
        answer_b: "v. hesitate",
        answer_c: "v. forget",
        answer_d: "v. speak",
        correct_answer: "b"
      },
      {
	id: 6,
        question: "Huawei, a telecoms giant, is in the blacklist since May over concerns that Chinese spooks use its gears to spy on America.",
        answer_a: "n. watcher",
        answer_b: "n. worker",
        answer_c: "n. spy",
        answer_d: "n. soldier",
        correct_answer: "c"
      },
      {
	id: 7,
        question: "Huawei have been hoarding parts in anticipation of a ban and have sought other suppliers",
        answer_a: "v. keeping for future",
        answer_b: "v. wasting",
        answer_c: "v. needing",
        answer_d: "v. buying",
        correct_answer: "a"
      },
      {
	id: 8,
        question: "A shortfall in recruitment led to the company being understaffed  ",
        answer_a: "n. abundance",
        answer_b: "n. deficit, less than needed",
        answer_c: "n. ware",
        answer_d: "n. team",
        correct_answer: "b"
      },
      {
	id: 9,
        question: "I think it's important not to downplay the significance of the event.",
        answer_a: "v. play carefully",
        answer_b: "v. enhance",
        answer_c: "v. play hard",
        answer_d: "v. minimize importance of",
        correct_answer: "d"
      },
      {
	id: 10,
        question: "If we can get to the engine's innards we might find out what's making that noise.",
        answer_a: "n. internal organs",
        answer_b: "1",
        answer_c: "2",
        answer_d: "3",
        correct_answer: "a"
     }
]

export default questions;
